The next station is Tokyo.
The doors on the left side will open.
>> [music]
[music]
>> You guys have no idea how sweaty I am
right now.
Da na na na
>> [music]
[music]
>> I had a video that was due like
yesterday and I was trying to edit that
on my flight here, so I didn't get much
sleep on the flight and I'm super jet
lagged, so I got like 4 hours of sleep
last night. And I'm actually wide awake.
I still wasn't able to finish the video,
so [snorts]
I'm going to work on that until Serena
wakes up. Yeah, I'm like stressing out.
I'm not even close to being finished.
I've been on my final steps of editing
for the past 10 hours of editing.
>> [music]
>> I'm on my way to get some hand soap and
some coffee.
I'm just going to get coffee.
Is this one plus one? One plus one?
Limit. Limit. Oh, okay.
I'm so confused. What?
Oh, nice.
I can't speak Japanese
in Japanese.
Look who's here, Serena. Hello.
>> [singing]
[music]
>> We got the strawberry diced fruit, egg
salad, and original whipped cream.
[music]
>> [music]
[singing]
>> And they have regular milk and then soy
milk.
Premium matcha latte with milk and soy
That's really strong. We got no sugar.
Because I got no sugar in Yeah.
Mmm, that's so good.
>> good.
Oh, no. That was good. That was worth
the wait.
>> Mhm.
This is like so good.
>> [music]
[music and singing]
[music]
>> I'm over stimulated right now.
Trying to see if they have the shoes
that I want.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Day two, we're going to Shinjuku today.
We're going to make daifuku. Yay!
>> [music]
>> So powerful.
[music]
>> Woah, love start with friendship. I
don't do friends to lovers.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, okay, baby.
[music]
>> I'm going to post this
on the gluttony.
>> [music]
>> Oh, very cute.
[music]
>> Maybe we go back to the blue bottle.
Yeah.
We thought this meant fifth floor, but
it's on this floor.
Oh my gosh.
We found it.
>> [music]
>> Right.
[singing]
[music]
>> We're going to try these two jellies.
This is
yogurt soda gummy.
This is something apple flavored.
>> [snorts]
>> That was good.
Mhm.
Tastes like milk.
Yo, that's good. That's really good.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Day three, we're going to Shibuya.
Hey.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I'll just try this.
I don't [music] think I'll like it that
much.
Carrot. Wait, is that a carrot?
Peach. That's cute.
It's like so ugly, it's cute, you know?
That's so cute.
I got this one. I wanted to buy five,
but they said I can only get [music]
one. I don't know, that doesn't make
sense to me, but
we'll go with it.
>> [music]
[music]
>> That's so good.
It's so good.
What else we experience?
Mhm.
Small.
We're at a club and there's literally no
one else here. It's just us. Where y'all
at?
Hello.
>> [music]
[music]
>> We're going to go to Harajuku. Harajuku.
We're going to go to Harajuku. We're
going to
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know if I should say it like
white. We're going to go to Harajuku and
do some shopping and then go to I'm
donuts, get some yummy donuts and
coffee. I was so hungover this morning.
>> [music]
>> Oh, ew.
Oh my god.
Cool.
That's a meal.
Oh my
We got strawberry [music] blueberry tea.
cream,
and pistachio.
Do you mind if I take this?
That was so good.
>> [music]
>> So crowded. [music]
So cute.
>> [music]
[music]
>> So cute.
Why am I struggling to open it?
Oh, it's like not open. Okay, okay.
Yeah.
Nauseous, dehydrated. Oh, thank you.
Do you want to do it with egg, cheese,
or just plain?
>> [music]
[music]
>> This
and then
that one.
Oh.
3 2 1
This is a fiber drink and it's supposed
to be good for constipation. I've not
pooped since coming to Japan. I took one
of these and like a fiber jelly, did not
work. So, I'm going to take two of
these. Hopefully,
I can poop.
>> [music]
>> It broke my leg.
[music]
>> What we wanted to I'm doing it
yesterday. We got our donuts and we went
upstairs to their seating area cafe. It
was a pretty full cafe so we ended up
standing. We were facing the wall facing
away from everyone. I hear the workers
say something in Japanese and everyone
goes silent in the cafe, right? And I
look back because I'm like why is
everyone so quiet? Every single person
in the cafe, like 15 people, were
staring at us. To Serena I was like, why
is everyone staring at us right now? And
then the worker says something again in
Japanese and I look to her and I'm like,
English? And then she says that we have
to order one drink per person to be able
to eat there. So I was like, oh okay.
Like imagine turning around and seeing a
bunch of people just being like
>> [music]
[music]
>> Beautiful color.
That's good. [music] That's good.
Beautiful.
Oh, it's hot.
>> [music]
>> Oh.
So cute.
>> What are those? Cannot be used.
All the jellies are so much cheaper here
than Don Quijote. I'm going to get some
just cuz.
>> [music]
>> We didn't know that was alcoholic. We
just thought it was sparkling water. I
mean yeah, it's just sparkling water.
And I was like, huh, it says 7%.
>> Why does it say 7%? Wait, but Nado's
like trying and we're like, it's just
>> Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> And the way you didn't taste the
alcohol, right?
Just taste it, it's sparkling water. Oh,
okay.
Oh my gosh, you cheated.
Dude.
>> [music]
>> Mhm.
That's good. Mhm.
>> [music]
>> It's the alcohol. Right.
Yeah.
Mhm.
>> [music]
[laughter]
>> No.
>> We finished a really good discount
because we were going to leave. He gave
us a calculator and was like, "Just
punch in a price." So, I punched in a
price.
No way.
>> [music]
>> I thought the cheese was stretchy,
[music] but it's not.
Wait, was it the tteokbokki in the first
shop?
Was it? It might have been okay. Oh my
god.
Wait, sorry. The No, it's okay. Yeah,
yeah. Oh, wait.
Oh, right.
I see her.
>> [music]
>> Aha.
Is it edible?
Oh, it is. Oh, it is. Oh my god, that
scared me.
I think I'm just too blind for them to
carry my power. Everywhere we've been
going, they said they either don't have
it or they just have one box. Yeah, I'm
a negative six.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Last day, we're going to claim my free
coffee.
Chicken, spicy chicken, pancakes with
maple and butter, eggs and grits. My
free coffee, I got it for free. Ooh,
this one is the spicy.
Oh, wait a minute. That one is
>> [laughter]
[music]
>> I need to change here.
>> This gets rid of [music] me. When I turn
to walk, I turn to walk.
Turn around.
I want to leave the party.
>> [music]
[music]